<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ramadan challenge</string>
    <string name="head">30 days,30 deeds</string>
    <string name="n1">Respectful Fasting</string>
    <string name="n2">Calm Composure</string>
    <string name="n3">Charitable Acts</string>
    <string name="n4">Prayerful Reflection</string>
    <string name="n5">Mannerly Conduct</string>
    <string name="n6">Seek Forgiveness</string>
    <string name="n7">Self-Discipline</string>
    <string name="n8">Community Involvement</string>
    <string name="n9">Mindful Detox</string>
    <string name="n10">Gratitude Practice</string>
    <string name="n11">Educate Yourself</string>
    <string name="n12">Spend Time with Family</string>
    <string name="n13">Health Consciousness</string>
    <string name="n14">Stay Hydrated</string>
    <string name="n15">Patience in Traffic</string>
    <string name="n16">Generosity</string>
    <string name="n17">Reflect on Quran</string>
    <string name="n18">Avoid Waste</string>
    <string name="n19">Stay Humble</string>
    <string name="n20">Forgive Others</string>
    <string name="n21">Avoid Excessive Spending</string>
    <string name="n22">Be Mindful of Language</string>
    <string name="n23">Pray for Others</string>
    <string name="n24">Sponsor a Fast</string>
    <string name="n25">Seek Knowledge</string>
    <string name="n26">Express Love and Kindness</string>
    <string name="n27">Reflect on Blessings</string>
    <string name="n28">Simplify Life</string>
    <string name="n29">Practice Self-Reflection</string>
    <string name="n30">Plan Zakat Distribution</string>
    <string name="d1">Observing fasting with reverence and mindfulness towards its spiritual significance and obligations.</string>
    <string name="d2">Maintaining a serene and composed demeanor, especially during challenging situations or conflicts.</string>
    <string name="d3">Engaging in acts of kindness and generosity towards others, particularly those in need.</string>
    <string name="d4">Taking time for introspection and spiritual contemplation through prayers and meditation.</string>
    <string name="d5">Behaving with courtesy, politeness, and respect towards others in words and actions.</string>
    <string name="d6">Humbly seeking pardon and forgiveness for any wrongdoings or transgressions.</string>
    <string name="d7">Exercising control and restraint over ones desires and impulses to adhere to moral and ethical principles.</string>
    <string name="d8">Participating actively in community activities and initiatives for the collective welfare.</string>
    <string name="d9">Practicing mindful habits to detoxify the mind from negative thoughts and influences.</string>
    <string name="d10">Cultivating a habit of expressing gratitude for blessings and acknowledging the goodness in life.</string>
    <string name="d11">Continuously seeking knowledge and understanding, particularly about religious teachings and practices.</string>
    <string name="d12">Prioritizing quality time with family members to strengthen bonds and foster harmony.</string>
    <string name="d13">Being mindful of ones physical health and well-being through balanced nutrition and lifestyle choices.</string>
    <string name="d14">Ensuring adequate hydration, especially during fasting periods, to maintain optimal health.</string>
    <string name="d15">Exercising patience and tolerance while navigating through traffic or dealing with transportation delays.</string>
    <string name="d16">Displaying a generous and giving attitude towards others, whether through material possessions, time, or support.</string>
    <string name="d17">Contemplating and pondering upon the teachings and wisdom found in the Quran.</string>
    <string name="d18">Being mindful of resource consumption and minimizing wastage of food, water, and other resources.</string>
    <string name="d19">Cultivating humility and modesty in behavior and interactions with others.</string>
    <string name="d20">Letting go of resentment and bitterness by extending forgiveness to those who have wronged us.</string>
    <string name="d21">Exercising prudence and moderation in financial matters to avoid unnecessary expenditures.</string>
    <string name="d22">Using respectful and considerate language, avoiding hurtful or offensive speech.</string>
    <string name="d23">Offering prayers and supplications for the well-being and happiness of others.</string>
    <string name="d24">Supporting or sponsoring fasting individuals by providing them with iftar meals or other forms of assistance.</string>
    <string name="d25">Actively pursuing education and enlightenment, seeking knowledge from various sources.</string>
    <string name="d26">Demonstrating love, compassion, and kindness towards others through words and actions.</string>
    <string name="d27">Taking time to acknowledge and appreciate the blessings and privileges in ones life.</string>
    <string name="d28">Simplifying ones lifestyle and priorities to focus on essentials and reduce unnecessary complexity.</string>
    <string name="d29">Engaging in introspection and self-assessment to foster personal growth and improvement.</string>
    <string name="d30">Thoughtfully planning and distributing Zakat (charitable giving) to those in need according to Islamic principles.</string>
    <string name="e11"></string>
</resources>